White-tiled walls and a buzzing light A heavy
door locked up so tight My body's weak, my needs
are clear But that's not why you brought me here
The hunger's now and thirst is real But all I'm
ever forced to feel Is the chilling echo in this
space And the rising fury On your face
Just let me be invisible Just let me crawl under a
stone Your voice is razor indivisible Just
leave me, leave me all alone Inside this past
skull I can hear
There's no escape, no way to flee.
And now the screaming finally starts Tearing
all my seams apart It's all my fault, this whole
cursed trip The poison dripping from your lip
The walls are closing, tile and steel This
nightmare's finally getting real You blame my
chair, you blame my needs You're planting
bitter hateful seeds
Just let me be invisible Just let me crawl under a
stone Your voice is razor indivisible Just
leave me, leave me all alone Inside this past, go
lock and key
There's no escape, no way to flee
. .
Just let me be invisible Just let me crawl under a
stone Your voice is a razor indivisible Just
leave me, leave me all alone Inside this past, go
lock and key There's
no escape, no way to flee